Vincent Price Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Sears, Roebuck and Company Files, 1943-1976 (Box 57-111)
  - National Treasures (Box 64)
    - Cookbooks
      - Publicity, 1966, 1971
      - Stravon Publishers, 1966-1969, (2 folders)
    - Correspondence (Box 65)
      - Adler, Eugene M., 1963-1966
      - Baldridge, Letitia, 1964-1969, (2 folders)
      - Butler, R. D., 1964-1969, undated, (5 folders)
      - Dunn, Malcolm, 1964-1969, undated, (5 folders) (Box 66)
      - Gannoway, Irl, 1965-1966, undated
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1964-1965, (5 folders)
        - 1966-1967, (2 folders) (Box 67)
      - Odell, Douglas, 1965-1966, (3 folders)
      - Romaine, Lawrence, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
      - Schwartz, Marvin, 1964-1967
      - Sundheim, Harry G., Jr., 1963-1966, (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - Departments
      - Bath, slumber, linen, 1964-1967
      - Building materials, 1965-1966
      - Curtains, draperies, 1964-1967
      - Family recreation, sporting goods, 1965
      - Fencing, urban and rural equipment, 1966
      - Floor covering, 1964-1967
      - Furniture, 1964-1969, undated, (2 folders)
      - Hardware, power tools, lawn equipment, 1966
      - Home fashion accessories, 1964-1969, undated, (5 folders) (Box 69)
      - Housewares, 1964-1966
      - Jewelry, 1965-1966
      - Lawn and garden, 1965
      - Lighting fixtures, fireplace accessories, 1952, 1965-1966
      - Notions, 1965-1967
      - Paints, wall coverings, 1964-1966, undated
      - Photographic, business equipment, educational and general stationery, 1966-1967 (Box 70)
      - Plumbing, heating, 1965-1966
      - Retail sales promotion, 1965-1967
      - Yard goods, paper patterns, 1966-1967
    - Insignia, 1965, undated
    - Meetings and planning materials, 1964-1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Merchandise
      - Critiques, undated
      - Inventory lists, 1965-1966
      - Retail product listing, 1965
    - Publicity (Box 71)
      - Clippings, 1964-1966, 1972, (2 folders)
      - Promotional materials, 1966, (2 folders)
    - Reports
      - Colors, 1964
      - Historical background, undated
    - Reproduction of items
      - General, 1964-1965
      - Objects in warehouse, 1965
    - Research
      - Accessories
        - Bath, undated
        - Decorative, 1963-1967, undated, (5 folders) (Box 72)
        - Kitchen, 1967, undated
      - Appliances, 1965, undated (Box 73)
      - Bedding, 1963-1965, undated, (2 folders)
      - Candles, 1967, undated
      - Ceramic tile, 1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - China trade porcelain, 1943, 1964, undated
      - Christmas decorations, 1966, undated (Box 74)
      - Clocks, 1966, undated
      - Clothing, 1965, undated
      - Craft supplies, 1966
      - Crystal, 1966
      - Decks and fences, undated
      - Dinnerware, 1965-1966, undated
      - Doors, 1965-1967, undated, (2 folders)
      - Fabrics, undated
      - Fireplaces and barbeque equipment, 1966, undated
      - Floor treatments, 1965-1966, undated (Box 75)
      - Formica laminates, 1965, undated
      - Fountains, 1963-1966
      - Furniture
        - Garden, 1964-1967, undated, (3 folders)
        - Mexican, 1966, undated, (3 folders) (Box 76)
        - Office, 1965-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Traditional, 1964-1967, undated, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 77)
        - Unfinished, undated
      - Grills and room dividers, 1966, undated
      - Hardware, undated
      - Iron accessories and furniture, 1964-1965, undated
      - Lamps and lighting fixtures, 1966-1967, undated, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Landscaping, undated
      - Lettering and monogramming, 1966, undated
      - Mirrors, 1964
      - Moulding, 1965-1966, undated
      - Paint, 1966
      - Planters, 1965-1966
      - Rattan accessories and furniture, undated
      - Reference books, 1964, undated, (2 folders)
      - Roofs and skylights, 1966, undated
      - Rugs, 1966
      - Silverplate, 1966, undated
      - Sites (Box 79)
        - Arizona, 1966
        - California
          - Miscellany, 1949-1966, undated, (3 folders)
          - Missions, 1959-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Colorado, 1966
        - District of Columbia, undated
        - Georgia, undated
        - Hawaii, undated
        - Historic American Buildings Survey, 1961-1963
        - Illinois, 1964, undated
        - Louisiana, 1964, undated
        - Massachusetts, 1964-1966, undated (Box 80)
        - Mexico, 1963-1964
        - Missouri, 1964-1966, undated
        - Nevada, 1966
        - New Jersey, 1966
        - New Mexico, 1961-1966, undated
        - New York, 1964, undated
        - Oregon, 1966
        - South Carolina, 1964, undated
        - Texas
          - Miscellaneous locations, 1966, undated, (3 folders)
          - San Antonio, 1964, undated
          - Varner-Hogg State Park, 1963-1966 (Box 81)
        - Utah, 1964-1966, undated
        - Virginia, 1964
        - Washington, 1964-1966, undated
        - West Virginia, 1966
        - Wyoming, 1966
      - Stairways, 1966, undated
      - Towels and bedspreads, 1965-1966, undated
      - Toys, 1945
      - Weathervanes, 1964-1966, undated
      - Window treatments, 1966, undated, (2 folders)
    - Shipments
      - Insurance claims, 1964-1965
      - Items sent and received, 1964-1967, undated, (2 folders)
  - Projects and products (Box 82)
    - Art
      - Course, 1963-1966
      - Supplies, 1963-1966
    - Charm school
      - General, 1965-1969
      - "Sears and the Contemporary Woman," 1969, (2 folders)
      - "Sears School for Young Charmers," 1965
    - Chocolates, 1965-1968, undated
    - Christmas
      - Cards, 1963-1966
      - Ornaments, 1964
    - Commercials, 1968-1972, undated
    - Decorating school (Box 83)
      - General, 1971-1975, undated, (2 folders)
      - "How to Decorate Your Home," 1972
    - Father's Day gifts, 1964-1965
    - Home movie outfit, 1964-1965
    - Lamp, 1964-1965
    - Michelangelo Bible
      - Clippings, 1964-1965
      - Correspondence, 1963-1967, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Text, 1964, undated
    - Miscellaneous activities and ideas, 1963-1974, undated (Box 84)
    - Perfume program
      - "Flame," 1964, undated
      - General, 1964, undated
      - "Stampede"
        - General, 1964-1966, undated
        - Package design, 1964, undated
        - Publicity, 1965
        - Research materials, 1963, undated
    - Sears Women's Classic of St. Lucie, Port St. Lucie, Fla., 1971-1974
    - Spices, 1964
    - Television antennas, 1964
  - Vincent Price Collection of Fine Art
    - Art frauds, 1960-1967 For additional material see Sargent, John Singer, Container 103
    - Artists
      - In collection
        - Abril, Ben, 1964
        - Ackerman, Frank E., 1964-1966
        - Acosta, Manuel, 1965
        - Ancevicius, Dalia, 1965
        - Anderson, Les, 1965-1966
        - Appelbaum, David H., 1966
        - Arnott, Kaye, 1966
        - Asmar, Alice, 1963-1965
        - Baer, Howard, 1966 (Box 85)
        - Banys, Nijole, 1965
        - Barber, John, 1965-1969
        - Baumruker, Rose, 1965
        - Beamish, Alice, 1965
        - Bentley, Wilder, 1965-1967
        - Bini, Enrico, 1965-1966, undated
        - Blair, Streeter, 1962-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Broduer, Donald, 1965
        - Brown, Ginny, 1964-1966
        - Button, John, 1965
        - Carlson, E. Thor, 1965-1966
        - Carpenter, Evelyn Delight, 1964-1965
        - Carrillo, Edward, 1964
        - Catalog of names, 1966
        - Cederberg, Ohm, 1963-1967
        - Charlot, Jean, 1965
        - Chee, Robert, 1965
        - Court, Hazel, 1964-1965
        - Crawford, Richard, 1964-1967
        - Cunningham, Florence, 1965
        - Dailey, Charles, 1965 (Box 86)
        - Dali, Salvador, 1963-1964
        - Dargis, Alfonsas, 1965-1966
        - Dignan, Eleanor, 1966
        - Dorland, Thom, 1965
        - Duarte, John, 1965
        - Dunn, Nate, 1965-1967
        - Edwards, Ethel, 1965
        - Evans, William J., 1966
        - Everson, Landis, 1965
        - Farley, E. Amsterdam, 1965
        - Fattig, Anne, 1965
        - Fiore, Joseph, 1965
        - Fretheim, Conrad W., 1967
        - Friesz, Ray, 1964-1966, undated
        - Gartin, Paul, 1965
        - Gecse, Helene, 1965
        - Gervasi, Frank, 1965
        - Goldberg, Aron, 1963-1966
        - Green, Michael, 1966, undated
        - Harvey, Robert, 1966, undated
        - Helbock, Elaine, 1966
        - Henley, Dick, 1965
        - Henrie, Paul Blaine, 1964-1970
        - Hewitt, Robert Reynolds, 1965
        - Hill, Bobby, 1966
        - Hilsop, Juanita, 1964-1966, undated
        - Hittman, Karl, 1965-1966
        - Hollander, Gino, 1965-1966
        - Hulett, Ralph, 1965
        - Hurd, Peter, 1964-1966
        - Jovanovic, Bogdan, 1964-1968
        - Katz, Alex, 1965
        - Kehew, George, 1965-1967
        - Kivela, Aarne, 1965-1967, undated
        - Kloss, Gene, 1965, undated
        - Korling, Peter, 1965
        - Langlais, Bernard, 1965 (Box 87)
        - Lioutikoff, Alexander (Sachal), 1965-1966
        - Longley, Bernique, 1965
        - Malone, Robert R., 1966
        - Marcucci, Sallie, 1965-1966
        - Massey, Dorothy Hardin, 1965
        - Meigs, John, 1965-1967
        - Miller, Gerhard C. F., 1965-1966
        - Miscellaneous, 1963-1967, undated, (3 folders)
        - Mitchell, Robert, 1965-1966
        - Moore, Marilyn, 1965
        - Moore, Mary, 1965
        - Morse, Samuel, 1965-1966
        - Most, Howard, 1965-1966
        - Myer, Peter L., 1965
        - Neufeldt, Max, 1967-1968
        - Nichols, Dale, 1965-1967
        - Oaks, Shirley, 1964-1965
        - Perrin, Robert, 1966-1967
        - Roberts, George D., 1964-1967
        - Rogers, Charles B., 1965
        - Rose Margaret, Sister, 1964-1965
        - Rundall, Dee, 1966
        - Ruthling, Ford, 1965-1967
        - Sadowsky, Eugene, 1964-1965 (Box 88)
        - Sample, Richard, 1965
        - Santschi, Sally, 1965
        - Serio, Emilio, 1965
        - Shattuck, Ross, 1965
        - Sherry, William Grant, 1958-1967, undated
        - Simmonds, Julie, 1965
        - Sirry, Gazbia, 1965-1967
        - Smith, Warren, 1966-1967
        - Sodeika, Zita, 1965
        - Solano, Theresa, 1965
        - Spiegel, Harvey, 1964-1966
        - Stancin, Jim, 1965
        - Stewart, Charles C., 1965-1966
        - Szabo, Joseph, 1967-1968
        - Taylor, Derrick, 1966-1967
        - Thomas, Robert, 1965-1966
        - Tripp, Russell, 1965-1967, undated
        - Vaicaitis, Vladas, 1965
        - Van Buren, Ingeborg, 1964-1965
        - Van Orden, Stuart C., 1965-1966
        - Vickers, Robert C., 1963-1967
        - Volpe, Richard, 1965-1966
        - Wacholz, Stan, 1965, undated
        - Walaitis, Edward, 1965, undated
        - Walker, Peter, 1965
        - Waterhouse, Russell, 1965
        - Watson, Robert, 1965-1966
        - Weber, Paul H., 1965-1966
        - White, Thomas F., 1965-1967
        - Whorf, Richard, 1965-1966, undated
        - Wilkerson, Raleigh, 1965
        - Williams, David, 1963-1967
        - Wyeth, Andrew, 1963-1966, undated
      - Rejected
        - A, 1963-1968
        - B, 1963-1968, undated, (4 folders) (Box 89)
        - C, 1962-1968, undated, (3 folders)
        - D, 1964-1969, undated, (2 folders) (Box 90)
        - E, 1963-1967, undated
        - F, 1963-1967, undated, (2 folders)
        - G, 1963-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - H, 1964-1968, undated, (3 folders) (Box 91)
        - I, 1963-1966
        - J, 1965-1968, undated
        - K, 1964-1968, (2 folders)
        - L, 1963-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 92)
        - M, 1961-1968, undated, (4 folders)
        - N, 1963-1968
        - O, 1964-1967, undated
        - P, 1963-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 93)
        - Q, 1965
        - R, 1963-1968, (2 folders)
        - S, 1963-1968, (4 folders)
        - T, 1963-1968, (2 folders) (Box 94)
        - U, 1965-1966
        - V, 1964-1968
        - W, 1964-1968, undated, (3 folders)
        - X, 1966
        - Y, 1965-1967
        - Z, 1965-1968
      - To consider (Box 95)
        - Miscellaneous, 1962-1968, undated, (4 folders)
        - Society of Western Artists, 1964-1966
    - Charts, reports, and analyses
      - Buyers' monthly reports, 1965-1966
      - Inventory, 1965-1966, undated See also Oversize
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1966, undated
      - Sales figures, 1963-1967, (4 folders) (Box 96)
    - Collections, 1962-1965, undated
    - Correspondence
      - Customers, 1962-1969, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1962-1963, (2 folders)
        - 1964-1967, undated (Box 97)
      - Sears personnel, 1962-1970, (3 folders)
    - Critiques, 1964-1965, undated
    - Framing
      - Correspondence, 1963-1966
      - Miscellany, 1963-1966
      - Shipping records and framing instructions
        - 1964
        - 1965-1966, undated, (4 folders) (Box 98)
      - Specification sheets, 1963-1964, undated, (4 folders)
      - Suppliers (Box 99)
        - Armand Lee and Co., 1965-1966, undated
        - Franklin Picture Frame Company, 1963-1966, undated
    - Graphics catalogs and mailings, 1963-1964, undated
    - History and background material, 1966, undated
    - Lawsuit regarding use of name, 1963-1967, undated, (2 folders)
    - Local stores, California, 1967
    - Meeting materials, 1965, (2 folders)
    - Merchandising guidelines, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, undated
    - Other department stores, 1965-1966 (Box 100)
    - Publicity
      - Atlanta, Ga., showing, 1965
      - Clippings
        - Canada, 1963
        - General, 1962-1970, undated, (7 folders)
        - New York, 1963 (Box 101)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1967, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1962-1966, undated
      - Promotional material
        - General, 1962, undated
        - Nebraska centennial exhibit, 1967
    - Price comparisons, 1962-1965, undated
    - Purchases
      - Bills of sale, 1962-1964
      - Foreign buying
        - Australia, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
        - England, 1964-1965
        - Hong Kong, 1965-1966
        - Italy, 1966-1967, undated
        - Japan (Box 102)
          - General, 1965
          - Haniwa material, 1965-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Thailand, 1965-1966
      - Galleries and dealers
        - Alan Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1965
        - Albright-Knox Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1963-1964, undated
        - Alfert, Max, 1966
        - Baker Collector Gallery, Lubbock, Tex., 1965
        - Beaconsfield Gallery, Bucks, England, 1964-1965
        - Beaux Arts Gallery, London, England, 1963-1964
        - Bright, Glory, 1965-1966
        - Carl's Indian Trading Post, Taos, N. Mex., 1965
        - Cummings, Willard, 1965-1966
        - The Drawing Shop, New York, N.Y., 1965-1966
        - E. Lorenz Borenstein Gallery, New Orleans, La., 1965-1967, undated, (2 folders)
        - Ernest Raboff Gallery, Los Angeles, Calif., 1966-1967
        - Fine Art Society, London, England, 1963-1964
        - Galleria 88, Rome, Italy, 1963-1968, (2 folders) (Box 103)
        - Gallery of John Nicholson, New York, N.Y., 1965-1970, undated
        - Gemini, G. E. L., Los Angeles, Calif., 1967
        - Glade Gallery, New Orleans, La., 1966
        - J. S. Maas and Co., London, England
          - General, 1964-1970, undated
          - Sargent, John Singer, paintings, 1964-1968, undated, (5 folders)
        - Jette, Ellerton M., 1965 (Box 104)
        - Larcada, Richard K., 1965-1968, undated
        - Maynard Walker Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1965
        - Meigs, John, 1965-1966, undated
        - Mercury Gallery, London, England, 1964-1966
        - Miscellaneous, 1962-1970, undated, (3 folders)
        - Morse, Peter, 1965, undated
        - Pierce Gallery, Oakland, Calif., 1966-1967
        - Portal Gallery, London, England, 1964
        - Powney, Christopher, 1964
        - R. M. Light and Co., Boston, Mass., 1962-1970, (2 folders) (Box 105)
        - Reed, O. P., 1962-1967, undated, (2 folders)
        - Rex Evans Gallery, Los Angeles, Calif., 1962-1968, undated
        - Roswell Museum and Art Center, Roswell, N. Mex., 1965
        - Schweitzer, M. R., 1965, undated
        - Simkin, Colin, 1965-1966
        - Snodgrass, Jeanne, 1965
        - Steed, Robert, 1965
        - Wightman, Bruce, 1966
        - Williamson, Mrs. H. R., 1965
        - Yeakel and Field, Laguna Beach, Calif., 1965
        - Zeitlin and Ver Brugge, Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1966
      - Loria, Jeffrey H., 1965, undated For additional material see Container 57, Loria, Jeffrey H. (Box 106)
      - Miscellaneous records, 1963-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Sundheim, Harry G., Jr., 1964-1968, (5 folders)
      - Trip file
        - Foreign
          - Africa, 1966
          - Australia and Asia, 1965, undated, (3 folders)
          - England, 1963-1969, undated, (5 folders) (Box 107)
          - India, 1965, undated
          - Italy, 1963-1966, undated, (4 folders)
          - Miscellaneous anticipated trips, 1964-1967, undated (Box 108)
          - Spain, 1967, undated
        - United States
          - California
            - Laguna, La Jolla, San Diego area, 1964-1966
            - Los Angeles area, 1963-1968, undated
            - Miscellaneous locations, 1966-1967, undated
            - San Francisco, 1956-1970, undated
          - District of Columbia, 1964-1967
          - Hawaii, 1963-1965
          - Illinois, 1966-1968
          - Miscellaneous anticipated trips, 1964-1968, undated
          - New York, 1965-1968, undated
    - Requests for employment, 1962-1967, undated (Box 109)
    - Shows
      - Brochures and catalogs, 1962-1966, undated
      - Packing lists, 1965, (3 folders)
      - Schedules, 1963-1967, (2 folders)
    - Travel schedules, 1963-1965
    - Vincent Price Gallery
      - Atlanta-Peachtree, Ga., 1966
      - Chicago, Ill. (Box 110)
        - Correspondence, 1966-1972, undated, (3 folders)
        - Exhibit materials, 1966-1971, undated, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1966-1970, undated
        - Publicity, 1966-1969 For additional material see Container 101, Publicity
        - Reference worksheets, 1970 (Box 111)
      - Dallas, Tex., 1966, undated
      - Los Angeles, Calif., 1965-1967, undated
- Speeches and Writings Files, 1931-1991 (Box 111-127)
  Holograph and typewritten manuscripts, notes and jottings, research notes, related correspondence, and clippings.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of writing and therein by title or topic.
  - Articles, 1958-1989, undated, (5 folders) (Box 111)
  - Autobiographical material, 1959, undated (Box 112)
  - Books
    - The Book of Joe
      - Draft, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1960-1968, undated
      - Reviews, 1961, undated
    - I Like What I Know
      - Clippings, 1959-1960, undated
      - Correspondence, 1959-1960, undated
    - Monsters, with V. B. (Vincent Barrett) Price
      - Correspondence
        - 1974-1977, (3 folders)
        - 1978-1984, (3 folders) (Box 113)
      - Draft, 1975-1978, undated, (10 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1981, undated (Box 114)
      - Notes and outlines, 1974-1975, undated
      - Publisher's revision, 1978-1979, undated, (4 folders)
      - Research material, undated, (2 folders)
      - Reviews, 1981-1982, undated
    - A Treasury of Great Recipes, with Mary Grant Price
      - Correspondence
        - 1963-1965, (4 folders)
        - 1966-1976, undated, (3 folders) (Box 115)
      - Draft, 1964, undated, (2 folders)
      - Publicity
        - Clippings, 1965-1972, (2 folders)
        - Promotional material and activities, 1965-1980, undated
      - Publishers (Box 116)
        - Bernard Geis Associates, 1963-1973, undated, (6 folders)
        - Doubleday and Co., 1968-1972
        - Grosset and Dunlap, 1977-1983
      - Recipes, undated (Box 117)
      - Restaurants, 1964-1965, undated
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1963-1966, 1971, undated, (2 folders)
    - Vincent Price: His Movies, His Plays, His Life, 1975-1978
    - The Vincent Price Treasury of American Art
      - Correspondence, 1970-1974, undated, (2 folders)
      - Draft, undated, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 118)
      - Lists, 1971-1972, undated
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Notes, undated
      - Research, undated, (4 folders)
  - Columns (Box 119)
    - Correspondence
      - Booke, Stephen, editor, 1966-1970, 1978, (3 folders)
      - Laro, Arthur, Chicago Tribune-New York News Syndicate, 1966-1970, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1970, (3 folders)
    - Drafts (Box 120)
      - 1966-1967, (7 folders)
      - 1967-1968, (8 folders) (Box 121)
      - 1969-1970, (7 folders) (Box 122)
    - Ideas, 1966-1968, undated, (3 folders) (Box 123)
    - Illustrations, undated
    - Miscellany, 1966-1970
  - Forewords and introductions, 1958-1975, 1981-1989, undated, (2 folders)
  - Ideas and proposed projects, 1959-1986, undated, (3 folders) (Box 124)
  - Lectures and addresses
    - "An Actor's Life for Me," undated
    - Art talks, 1963-1974, undated
    - "Dear Theo," incomplete, undated
    - "Descent from Cloud Nine," delivered upon receiving honorary degree, California College of Arts and Crafts, Oakland, Calif., June 3, 1955
    - Kapalua Wine Symposium speech, Maui, Hawaii, July 22, 1989
    - Miscellaneous, 1953, 1969, undated
    - "Paradise Lost" (on Paul Gauguin), undated
    - "Three American Voices," undated
    - Variety Clubs convention speech, Las Vegas, Nev., April 27, 1971 (Box 125)
    - "The Villains Still Pursue Me," undated
    - "What the Hell Do You Do with the Parsley?" 1963, undated
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1959, undated, (3 folders)
  - Notes and jottings, undated, (2 folders)
  - Poetry, 1931-1971, undated, (6 folders) (Box 126)
  - Tributes and appreciative statements (Box 127)
    - Anderson, Judith, 1988
    - Guinness, Alec, undated
    - Hayes, Helen, 1983
    - Hockney, David, 1990
    - Lorre, Peter, 1964
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1991, undated
    - Rosenberg, Edgar, 1987
  - Unidentified, undated.
- Stage, Screen, and Studio Files, 1935-1992 (Box 127-200)
  Scripts, programs, playbills, correspondence, telegrams, schedules and itineraries, contracts, clippings, storyboards, publicity and promotional materials, and other records relating to Price's acting roles and other performances and appearances as an entertainer and celebrity.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of activity and therein alphabetically by name of project or topic, except for the lecture and miscellaneous files which are arranged chronologically.
  - Commercials and promotions (Box 127)
    - American Dairy Association, 1981-1985, (3 folders)
    - Angostura Bitters, 1971-1973
    - Bantam Books, Agatha Christie Mystery Collection, 1987
    - Best Western Motels, 1973-1974
    - Birds Eye, 1971 (Box 128)
    - Busch Gardens, 1984-1988
    - Citibank, 1985
    - Cousins Submarines, 1984-1989
    - Creamettes, 1976-1977
    - Discount Travel International, 1985
    - Gaviscon, 1984-1987
    - Hallmark Creepy Classics, 1987
    - Haunted Hayrides, 1990-1991
    - Haywards Pickles, 1977-1981, 1987
    - Hitachi, 1976-1979
    - Infamous Cookies, 1977-1979
    - Krusteaz Baking Mix, 1979
    - The Masters Condominium, 1973
    - Merchants Bank, 1973-1974
    - Milton Bradley Co., 1974-1984
    - Miscellaneous spots, 1954-1991, undated, (2 folders)
    - Monster Vitamins, 1974-1975
    - NZ Listener, 1989-1990 (Box 129)
    - Nestle's Souptime, 1976-1977
    - Nikon, 1986-1987
    - Polaroid, 1984-1985
    - Price's Patent Candle Co., 1984-1985
    - Promise Toothpaste, 1981
    - Rueben's Restaurant, 1984
    - Samsung, 1984
    - Southwestern Bell, 1980, 1990
    - Sun Country, 1985-1986
    - Sun Giant Raisin, 1974
    - Tang, 1970-1971
    - Tilex, 1985-1989
    - Time-Life Books, 1984-1987
    - United Telecom, 1983-1984